NAME	NGUYEN TAN THO
	- Email: Thomasnguyendev@gmail
CONTACTS	- Phone: 0988 327 372
	- Skype :IDENGUYEN

## Overview

## Personal

Date of birth: 05/01/1989

Gender: Male

Personal Statement

 I've 5 years experience on development and 2 years with iOS, I has depth knowledge of iOS such as UIKit framework, Core Graphics for customized UI components - Core Data-framework, iCloud integration for data storage.
 nearly communication with mDNS(bonjour) and Bluetooth(LE vs classic) ....

## **Skills Summary**

• C++, Objective C, Swift, Javascript, Angularjs, NodeJS, PHP, CSS, JQuery, HTML

Technical Skills	
os	MAC, WINDOWS, LINUX
Languages	English
Databases	MySQL, NoSQL, MongoDB and Sqlite3.
Comms & Networks	Windows server, DHCP, FPT, TCP, UDP, Socket, REST_Full
Packages	
Methodologies & Tools	Xcode, Eclipse, Visual Studio, Jira, RedMine, SVN, Git, Rational Rose, Mantis, Lucidchart

Education, Qualifications & Special Achievements	
2011	Bachelor of Information Technology – Software Engineering, SaiGon University

NAME	NGUYEN TAN THO
CONTACTO	- Email: Thomasnguyendev@gmail
CONTACTS	- Phone: 0988 327 372 - Skype :IDENGUYEN

2014	Demandware developer
------	----------------------

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY		
Period	Company	Position
8/2015-Current	Harvey Nash VN	Senior software engineer
7/2013-8/2015	FPT telecom SJC	Senior software engineer
2011 – 7/2013	TiniPlanet SJC	Software engineer

## **RECENT ASSIGNMENTS**

ECAGO
24/12/2016
Doing (plan 9mons)
iOS Team leader
E-commerce applications as lazada
<ul> <li>Create task and assege task for member</li> <li>Check and review code of finish task</li> <li>Coder</li> </ul>
Media Layer, Notification, Core Services Layer, Swift, REST-full service, Webkit, Core data  Cocoa pod, cocoa control , lazy loading

Project	LG Watch manager
Duration	05/08/2015
Size (Days)	135 days
Position	Team leader
Project Description	LG Watch Manager connects watch to your iOS mobile device (phones and others).
	While connected, you can manage watch and installed apps via LG Watch Manager, and use features of the mobile device on a watch.
Му	Write document details design, TechProposal document
Responsibility	Create task and assege task for member
	Check and review code of finish task
	Research new technology for out team
	Coder
Technology	Media Layer, Notification, Core Services Layer, Swift, REST-full service, Webkit
	Core Bluetooth, mDNS (Bonjour service), Core data, caching
Droject	EDT MohiDay Viet Nam And Cambodia
Project	FPT MobiPay Viet Nam And Cambodia
Duration	05/04/2015
Duration	05/04/2015
Duration Size (Days) Position Project	05/04/2015  135 days  Team leader  Customer bill payments of the services provided as FPT, FPT Telecom net, TV
Duration Size (Days) Position	05/04/2015 135 days Team leader
Duration Size (Days) Position Project Description	05/04/2015  135 days  Team leader  Customer bill payments of the services provided as FPT, FPT Telecom net, TV FPT and FPT hosting  With features such as assigning employees chargeable Employees can search
Duration Size (Days) Position Project Description	05/04/2015  135 days  Team leader  Customer bill payments of the services provided as FPT, FPT Telecom net, TV FPT and FPT hosting  With features such as assigning employees chargeable Employees can search chargeable contract, directions for chargeable staff, update all the clients
Duration Size (Days) Position Project Description	05/04/2015  135 days  Team leader  Customer bill payments of the services provided as FPT, FPT Telecom net, TV FPT and FPT hosting  With features such as assigning employees chargeable Employees can search chargeable contract, directions for chargeable staff, update all the clients  • design flow chart, entity diagram
Duration Size (Days) Position Project Description	05/04/2015  135 days  Team leader  Customer bill payments of the services provided as FPT, FPT Telecom net, TV FPT and FPT hosting  With features such as assigning employees chargeable Employees can search chargeable contract, directions for chargeable staff, update all the clients  • design flow chart, entity diagram  • Create task and assege task for member
Duration Size (Days) Position Project Description	05/04/2015  135 days  Team leader  Customer bill payments of the services provided as FPT, FPT Telecom net, TV FPT and FPT hosting  With features such as assigning employees chargeable Employees can search chargeable contract, directions for chargeable staff, update all the clients  • design flow chart, entity diagram  • Create task and assege task for member  • Check and review code of finish task
Duration Size (Days) Position Project Description	05/04/2015  135 days  Team leader  Customer bill payments of the services provided as FPT, FPT Telecom net, TV FPT and FPT hosting  With features such as assigning employees chargeable Employees can search chargeable contract, directions for chargeable staff, update all the clients  • design flow chart, entity diagram  • Create task and assege task for member  • Check and review code of finish task  • Research new technology for out team

Project	Project: FPT Ticket
Duration	05/09/2014
Size (Days)	126 days
Position	Team leader
Project Description	Mobile Ticket is the ticket management system of incident can help users create, update, an overview of the status of each queue ticket, which will ease the management and handling of ticket in the shortest time
My	Development
Responsibility	Complete the assigned task and research new technology
	Development Mobile App as required
Technology	Objective C, REST-full service, Notification ,Using lib, Cocoa Touch Layer, Media Layer, Core Services Layer
Project	Project: FPT MobiNet
Duration	02/07/2014
Size (Days)	60 days
Position	Developer
Project Description	Report information worker group Deployment / Maintenance by date (contract number is assigned, the contract finishes and outstanding number of contracts). See list of outstanding contracts. Search and update ticket information, Search for customers, view customer status, number of connections. Allow MAC reset, reset passwords, open IPTV streams, kill the session. Report indicators deployment and maintenance services ADSL / FTTx (default within 1 month). Mobinet is a tool for check network by mobile devicemanagement and handling of ticket in the shortest time
My	Development
Responsibility	Complete the assigned task and research new technology
	Development Mobile App as required
Technology	Objective C, REST-full service, Notification ,Using lib, Cocoa Touch Layer, Media Layer, Core Services Layer

Project	Project: Jonathan
Duration	05/04/2013
Size (Days)	120 days
Position	Developer
Project Description	Jonathanadler is a website ecommerce very famous in England and America.
	Development e-commerce site ( www.jonathanadler.com )using Demandware cloud-based e-commerce platform technologies
My	Development
Responsibility	Complete the assigned task and research new technology
Technology	Java, Javascript, JSON,JQUERY, AJAX, HTML, CSS, SASS, SOAP
Project	Project: jooto
Duration	05/01/2013
Size (Days)	120 days
Position	Developer
Project Description	Develop Web Application (www.jooto.com) using backbonejs,bootstrap3, CSS, Ruby on rails and other technologies, Jooto (Joto) is a workflow management tool based on clouse
My	Development
Responsibility	Participating in code design, review, unit testing
Technology	Javascript, Backbonejs, Bootstrap3, JSON,AJAX, HTML5, Ruby On rails, MySQL
Project	Project: tiNiPlanet MMO Game
Duration	17/04/2012
Size (Days)	240 days
Position	Developer
Project Description	Developing MMO Game (www.tiniplanet.com ) using NodeJS, HTML5 and MongoDB, Develop Web Application using javascript, NodeJS, HTML5, CSS, and other technologies.Participating in code design, review, unit testing
My	Development
Responsibility	Participating in code design, review, unit testing
Technology	NodeJs, Express/CompoundJS FrameworkImpactJSJavascript, Impact Engine, Contruc2 Framework, JSON, HTML5, CSS3. NoSQL: MongoDB, Redis DB

Project	Project: 9k
Duration	07/11/2011
Size (Days)	150 days
Position	Developer
Project Description	Massive Multiplayer Game Online, Developing MMO pure Vietnam Game using C++(server Sword engine) and Flash ActionScript03 FrontEnd
My Responsibility	<ul><li>Development</li><li>Participating in code design, review, unit testing</li></ul>
Technology	Flash CS5, actionScript03, encryption algorithm,RSA,SHA, XOR,Sword engine, Path algorithms A*